

@

matheus.bernat@gmail.c om



+41 782310010



1007, Lausanne Switzerland

LINKS

 https://matheusbernat.github.io/

LANGUAGES

Portuguese, Swedish:

Native language

English:

C2

Proficient

French:

Intermediate

MATHEUS V. BERNAT

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hard-working last year master student with cumulated GPA 4.8/5.0, current exchange at EPFL for study year 21/22. Interested in pursuing a PhD in research fields of Computer Vision, Machine Learning and Signal Processing. Working experience at both academia and industry. Outside of school, I spend a lot of time following sports and F1!

EDUCATION

Msc: Signal And Image Processing Linköping University, 01/2023

Exchange: Signal And Image Processing **EPFL**, 01/2023 Exchange year (Msc 5th year)

Bachelor: Computer Science And Engineering **Linköping University**, 06/2020

SKILLS

- Python, C++, MATLAB.
- Python libraries: Pandas,
 Pytorch, OpenCV, Numpy.
- ROS.

- Mathematical modeling, statistical data analysis.
- Computer vision: 3D reconstruction, image classification, tracking.

RELEVANT COURSEWORK & PROJECTS

- Computer vision, neural networks, machine learning, applied data analysis, statistics for data science, bayesian networks, visual intelligence, image processing.
- Driverless team at LiU Formula Student, NLP team at Robocup@Home at FIA robotics.

WORK HISTORY

November 2019 - Current **Linköping university - Course Assistant**, Linköping, Sweden

Coaching 300 3rd year undergraduate students through the MATLAB computer labs of the courses Signals and Systems and Elements of AI.

June 2021 - August 2021 **UMS Skeldar - Engineering Intern**, Linköping, Sweden

Achieved mathematical model of sea and ship motion using physical modeling, control and simulations in MATLAB.

June 2020 - August 2020 **Veoneer - Software Engineer Intern**, Linköping, Sweden

Developed and bug-fixed one of Veoneer's internal websites and the front-end of a new "Follow-my-commit" for the company's developers using Vue.js.